So what did you
prepare for the meeting?
Wait, I need to
prepare something?
Ta-da!
This is what I prepared.
Of course, I called Mommy to
help me with what I’d prepare here.
And we also have
chicken, we have noodles...
for long life.
And of course,
our specialty, barbecue!
Yes,
- this setup is necessary.
- What?
What are you trying to say?
This is all about drugs.
I already signed the contract.
Are you serious, Mr. Roswell?
Hey, who gave you that?
I’m not allowed to
say Zeke gave it to me.
He said it’s a secret.
Zeke?!
Well, I’m glad to finally meet the
woman Mr. Roswell’s marrying.
Huh?!
Mr. Roswell is getting married?
Certificate of Marriage?
I’m married here to Mr. Roswell?
He's like my grandpa's age!
He’s not Mr. Roswell.
If he’s not Mr. Roswell,
then who is?
I’m Ezekiel Roswell.
And we’re married.
Huh?
I’m married here to Mr. Roswell?
He looks like my grandpa!
Zeke!
Huh?
Are you punishing me
because...
Zeke and I took the ring?
I’m sorry, but I’ll
return this to you.
Please don’t punish me.
There, I’m going home now.
I’ll tell Mommy about you.
Report?
Tell on us?
Zeke?
Sir, I’ll go ahead.
Oh!
Wait!
What is this?
Why is he leaving?
We just got married and
you’re already leaving?
Is that how it is, huh, Zeke?
Is that really how he acts?
We just got married and
you’re already walking out?
It literally just happened!
What about later on?
Ah, stupid girl.
He’s not Mr. Roswell.
If he’s not Mr. Roswell,
then who is?
I’m Ezekiel Roswell.
And we’re married.
Is this for real?
Are we really married?
You signed the documents, dear.
So, yes.
You’re married.
This is not real.
This isn’t happening.
Ow.
That hurts.
It’s real.
It’s real!
How did that even
become an official marriage?
Isn't a wedding supposed to have
a wedding gown, a
cake, bridesmaids.
I didn’t even get to walk
down the aisle with this music...
There's a difference between
a wedding and a marriage.
Huh?
Shut the fuck up, Lamperouge.
- Hey.
- Oh?
This driver’s gone crazy.
- Hey, hey.
- Let me borrow your phone.
- I’m calling a mental hospital.
Aemie, Aemie, stop.
You might touch
something else there.
You can’t just
touch any guy like that anymore.
Remember.
You’re a married woman now!
What's wrong with this one?
Why does your
friend keep laughing?
This one's crazy and so are you!
You’re both crazy!
You’re an angel, a
driver, a doppelganger!
And now you’re saying
you’re Mr. Roswell?
Why can’t you just admit you
came from a mental hospital?
Huh? Go back there!
Take him with you.
Bring your cop friend with you!
Since when did I become a cop?
Then why are you like that?
Wait, I just signed something.
And suddenly I’m married?
I didn’t even say “I do.”
Oops.
Got you.
You just said it.
Stop yelling.
You can't do anything
about it anymore.
We are married.
Shut the fuck up, Lamperouge.
You're worsening the situation.
Relax, Mr. Roswell.
I’m just entertained
by your wife.
You’re actually
lucky to have her.
Right?
Whatever.
Here you go, husband.
Thank you, wife.
Wow.
How do you like it?
It's perfect, wife.
Well, I don't expect anything
less from my perfect wife.
Anything for my perfect husband.
So good.
Wow.
Off to work.
Have a good day driving around.
I told you I’m not a driver.
Oh.
Whatever you say, husband.
Hey, woman.
We're here already.
What do you mean, ‘here’?
Here?
Hey.
Where did you
bring me this time?
You talk too much.
Just follow me.
Wow.
Whose mansion is this, Zeke?
It’s beautiful!
Is this your mansion, Zeke?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Wow.
This doesn’t even feel
like a mansion anymore.
This feels like a palace.
Wow,
it’s so beautiful!
It’s huge.
Wow.
Wow Zeke,
this is like ten times
the size of our house.
Welcome to your new home.
Huh?
How come?
We’re sharing this?
Obviously.
We're married.
Is that how it works?
Wow.
My house is huge!
Oh my god!
I made it!
I made it.
Oh.
Our house.
Is that okay?
Zeke...
can I make this pink?
Which part?
All of this.
Imagine the walls pink, the
tables, the chairs, everything pink.
Wouldn’t that be nice?
You’ve got a lot of ideas.
Hey, wait.
Zeke,
where are the people here?
There’s none.
None?
What do you mean none?
Where did they go?
You know what, maybe
you should just sleep.
Huh?
Oh.
Okay.
Zeke is something else.
His palace is so huge and yet,
this is where I’m sleeping?
Woah.
Honestly, though,
it's pretty cold.
I guess this is how
rich people’s tiles are.
Cold.
Oh well.
Still a win even
without a pillow.
Hey, woman!
What are you doing there?
Stop bothering me.
Someone’s trying to sleep here.
If you don't want to sleep,
at least let me sleep.
Zeke!
You scared me!
You’re gonna give me nightmares!
Why are you lying there?
You said sleep, right?
Idiot!
Not there, in the room.
Oh!
You didn’t say I
had a room here.
You know what.
You’re just like my cousin.
You're both
confusing to talk to.
You talk too much.
Did you see that?
He was smiling.
Hey, woman, hurry up!
Hey!
Hey, wait!
I don’t have a map
here. I’ll get lost!
Zeke!
Wow!
Damn!
This place is huge!
This is bigger than our kitchen
and living room combined!
Hey!
The bed is so soft!
I’m not used to this.
Well,
you better get used
to this kind of life...
wife.
Wife?
Why is he lying next to me?
Isn’t this my bed?
Is he sleeping here too?
Why does it feel like
he’s tempting me?
Like he wants to play?
If you know what I mean.
Oh my god, guys!
Send help!
What if I give in on the first day?!
Oh my god!
Lord, please help me!
Zeke!
What are you doing, Zeke?!
Sorry, sorry. Okay...
let’s take it slow.
Okay, game.
Game, game.
♪ Mom, Dad, I want some bread. ♪
♪ Sister, Brother, I want some coffee. ♪
♪ Whatever I want, you’ll follow. ♪
♪ If you mess up, I’ll pinch you! ♪
One.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you yelling?
Why are you taking
your clothes off?
It's hot!
Then why are you
getting closer to me?
Idiot!
You're sitting on this.
Oh.
Sorry.
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
To my room.
We’re not sleeping
next to each other?
You wish.
I have my own room.
You wish! I have my own room.
Cuz.
What time is it, why
didn’t you wake me up?
Oh right,
I didn’t sleep at home!
I’m dead.
What’s this?
To Aemie Roswell,
I forgot to give you
our wedding ring.
I’ll be home early later
so don't you dare go somewhere else.
Then go home.
Who do you think you are?
Your husband, Ezekiel Roswell!
Oh my god.
Oh, it's Zeke.
Another ring?
I already have one.
Oh, but this one’s different.
It's plain round.
I’m gonna look like a jeweler.
Oh!
I’ll move it to the other hand.
So my cuz won’t notice.
There.
So they won’t ask
too many questions.
To Aemie...
Roswell.
Is Roswell really
my last name now?
Are we really married?
Am I really married to Mr.
Ezekiel Roswell?
I'm hungry.
Oh, god.
Aemie's really dead meat.
I’ve been trying to
call her since last night
and she didn’t even go home?
Didn't she say
anything to her mom?
That’s exactly
what I find strange.
She didn't even seem worried.
Whenever Aemie's even
just a few minute's late,
she'd already be
calling every saint she knows.
But last night, she didn’t
seem bothered at all.
I don’t know, maybe she
knows where Aemie is right now.
What if we call the police?
I even tried calling.
Her phone is still off!
Dude, calm down.
If only she knew how
cute your gift is, Nico.
I'm sure she'll rush here.
But if she doesn’t
come to school,
are we gonna
postpone our plans later?
Actually, we don’t have to.
We have a date.
Or do you want to
go on a double date?
Say that again and I’m
seriously gonna stomp you.
- Momo...
- What?
Where is Moo anyway?
There she is.
Where did you go last
night, Aemie Romero?
Cuz.
I’ll explain.
It better be a good
explanation because.
I’ve been going crazy worrying
about you since last night.
And us too.
We were really
worried about you.
Yeah, seriously. Especially
that one over there.
Oh! Hi, Moo!
Careful, Nico.
Aemie might melt.
Huh?
Why would I melt?
I’m not ice cream.
Aemie, what date is it already
and you still haven’t explained?
Maybe you want to...
- Let’s go.
Calm down, Momo.
Be calm.
We still have class.
Bye, guys.
Don't let Nico
melt you, Aemie girl.
- Psst, hey.
- Let’s go.
Nico, take care of Aemie, okay?
- Dude, take care.
- We're not done!
Bye, Aemie!
- Bye!
- Bye.
Why...
why do they all seem so worried
that you might melt me?
Moo?
Do you have superpowers now?
Hey!
Moo, can you melt people now?
Moo, what are you even saying?
Oh, wait.
Do you have class?
Yeah, I do.
But I was late.
I went there earlier and
they said I’m excused.
- Oh, really?
- I honestly don’t know why.
- That’s cool, right?
- Yeah, that’s cool!
Hey, wow!
So cute!
Me or the puppy?
Both.
Well, yeah.
What?
Do you want to eat?
Yeah.
I’m really hungry, I’ve
been starving since earlier.
I rushed going here.
Alright, let’s go.
Let’s go to our hangout spot?
Okay, sure. Game, game!
Alright, okay.
- Here, hold the puppy.
- Hey, so cute!
He's prepared.
Let’s go!
Cutie! Cutie!
Wait.
Did I hear that right?
You want me to find you a cat?
Not just any cat,
but a really cute one.
Why do you need a cat?
The fuck do you
care, Lamperouge?
Just find one for me.
When do you need it?
Later.
Later?
Son of a cat.
Where am I
supposed to find a cat?
Most beautiful cat.
Oh no!
Your puppy is so cute, Moo.
Yeah, right?
Oh, but that’s not mine, Moo.
So Moo’s a dog-napper.
That’s crazy.
Isn’t what he earns from
acting and modeling enough?
Why does he have to
steal someone’s puppy?
Moo, I have something
to confess to you.
Here we go.
Here we go!
I'm telling you guys, he's about
to admit he's a dog-napper.
Really!
I’m telling you, hold me back.
I'll totally scold him!
It’s just that...
Well, uh...
Come on, Moo, just admit it.
I won’t get mad.
But you know what,
Moo? If I were you...
I’d return this
puppy to its owner.
What’s gotten into you?
You’re such a decent person.
Why would you steal
someone else’s puppy?
Don’t laugh.
There are so many
stray dogs out there.
You could’ve just picked one up.
At least no one gets hurt.
I didn’t steal it, Moo.
There you go again.
You just said earlier
it wasn’t yours.
It’s not.
I bought it.
For you.
Really?
Yes!
This is mine?
Yes.
- Happy Valentine's Day, Moo!
- Yay! This is mine.
Thank you!
Oh my god!
You’re so cute!
Does it have a name?
You name it.
Okay, okay.
What if...
we call it Aemie?
That works!
That’s the best name ever!
Because you’re both cute!
But...
it’s a boy.
You’re a boy!
I got it.
What if we call him Eisz,
so it matches my name?
Oh wow, he agrees.
He likes it.
Alright then.
From now on, your name is...
Okay, okay, Baby Eisz!
Baby Eisz! That’s so cute!
You’re so cute, Baby Eisz.
Your name is Baby Eisz now.
Hey, Moo.
Why?
Moo.
Listen carefully to
what I’m about to say.
Okay, go ahead. What is it?
Aemie,
from the moment I met you,
I already felt
something different.
At first, I thought I
was just mistaken.
But,
as I got to know you more,
as we got closer to each other,
that’s when I realized that...
Moo.
A wedding ring?
Oh!
Yeah.
And the other one is
an engagement ring.
But this one earlier.
Here, this one.
I just got this earlier.
Oh no.
Hey, Moo.
Don’t be sad, Moo.
Oh, do you want a ring too?
Here.
I’ll give you one.
You might say I’m being
greedy having two rings.
Just,
don’t tell Zeke I
gave it to you, okay?
He’ll get mad if he finds out I didn’t
charge you just because we’re friends.
We’re just friends?
Hey!
Come on now.
You’re being too much.
So sensitive.
Fine, it’s yours.
There, don’t be
shy. Take it home.
Go home early later, okay?
Don't you dare go
somewhere else.
I’m dead.
I need to go home.
Are you leaving me?
Hey, Moo. Wait.
No, no.
I’m not leaving you, Moo. Wait.
Hey, don’t be too sad.
I’m sure the one waiting for me
won’t mind if I
get home a bit late.
That guy’s really busy, Zeke.
Moo.
Do you want me to tell a joke?
Oh, uh, sure.
Okay.
There are...
three stupid friends
squeezing into one bed.
There's...
Juan, Pedro, and Berting.
Juan said to Berting, Berting...
Berting, the bed's too crowded!
Go lie down on the floor!
Then?
Then Berting lay
down on the floor.
Then Pedro said,
Berting, okay, you can
come back up on the bed now.
There’s space again.
You can lie down here now.
They’re so dumb, right?
How?
What?
What’s funny about that?
Well, it makes sense, right?
Berting got off the bed,
then when there was
space again, he came back.
That makes sense, right?
What’s wrong with that?
I don’t know with Moo.
He just didn't get
a wedding ring
and now his
mind's all over the place.
That wasn’t funny.
The fuck took you so long?
Mr. Roswell.
You said I had to
find not just any cat,
but the cutest cat.
Of course I put in effort, right?
I went everywhere.
Now, look at this.
Look at it.
It’s beautiful, right?
You can’t say I’m not
the most trustworthy,
most efficient person you know.
If you asked someone
else to do that,
it would probably take them a
month to find a cat that beautiful.
But since you assigned it to
someone as handsome as me,
I used my charm.
Voila!
You have the nicest, cutest
cat in the whole fucking world.
Next time,
make it harder.
You can leave now.
That’s it?
No reward?
Or at least a thank you?
Don’t you have anything
for drinks or girls?
Nothing.
That cat is for Aemie, right?
Look at you.
I thought you
only fell for the cat.
The fuck are you talking about?
Looks like you’re
falling for her.
You want to fall
off a cliff instead?
This is cute.
Don't touch that.
You even bought flowers.
What?
It's Valentine's.
She's my wife.
What’s the problem with that?
Right.
I’m not saying
that’s a bad thing.
It even makes you look good.
Get the fuck out of here.
- Okay.
- Now!
Alright, I’m leaving.
Goodbye.
Lover boy.
Get out!
Why do I have to be
home this fucking early?
Just because I'm gonna
give this goddamn cat?
Will that girl even like you?
Fuck!
Why am I acting like this?
I'm just gonna
give a goddamn gift.
As a thank you?
But why?
Because she married me?
Whatever.
I’ll just give this to
her because I want to.
That’s it.
Hey, woman!
Where the hell is she?
Bye, Moo!
Thanks for dropping me off.
Alright, you can go now.
Okay, go on, go on.
Bye-bye!
Mommy! I missed you, Mommy!
Ow!
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry I didn’t
tell you last night.
Things just happened, Mommy.
But I’ll tell you everything.
Ow!
Mommy, please. I’ll explain.
Let me explain.
You don’t need to explain.
Why, are you
disowning me, Mommy?
You don’t want me anymore?
You’re out late at night?
What is that?
That’s not right for
a married woman.
I didn’t raise you like that,
Aemie Romero-Roswell.
Out late?
I just got here, I...
What...
What did you call me?
What time is it?
And you’re still here.
Your husband might
be worried about you.
How did you know
I’m married, Mommy?
You know what, go home.
Right now.
Hey, Mommy!
- Who told you that?
- Come on.
Huh?
Mommy, who told you that?
- How did you know?
- Taxi, taxi!
- Oh, there’s a passenger.
- Wait.
Who is this?
Just get another taxi.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Here, take her home, okay?
- Where do you live?
- Here!
- Give him your new address.
- We were here first.
- Okay? Say hi to Zeke for me.
- This is so annoying.
- Be a good wife, Baby Ae.
- Okay? Be a good wife!
- Mommy!
- Bye!
- Mommy.
Oh my god.
It was so hard to
get a ride earlier.
Was it hard?
You know, there are
a lot of taxis over there.
- There, there!
- It’s traffic!
- It’s so hard to get a ride.
- There!
They might beat you to it.
Damn it!
Fuck!
I've been waiting for
her for three hours.
She's not even answering
her goddamn phone.
Fuck!
You know,
that woman is such a headache.
We’re here, Baby Eisz.
Thank you, mister.
I’m dead.
Zeke is here.
I’m screwed, he’s gonna scold me.
Baby Eisz,
help me explain to Zeke, okay?
I’m sure when he sees
you, he’ll find you cute.
He won’t scold me.
Wait.
Hey.
Who broke this?
Oh no!
Zeke?
I’m here.
Keep quiet, Baby Eisz.
Zeke?
Do you know what time it is?
Oh no.
Where is he?
Zeke?
Hey, woman.
Ah!
Hey!
I’m asking you.
You’re there.
I thought you were a ghost.
Uh, well...
I don’t know.
Why don’t you check?
Sorry, Zeke.
My phone died.
I really don’t know the time.
There.
Just check your watch
so you know what time it is.
Or does that not work either?
Hey, do you want me to
come with you to the market?
You can buy a watch there.
It’s only 150.
With all your money,
you could buy a lot.
You could probably
buy like twenty.
So you won’t have to
keep asking me for the time.
Want to go?
I’ll go with you.
Oh.
Zeke
is that a stuffed toy?
Wait, why is there
a cat there, Zeke?
I should be the one asking you.
Why do you have a dog?
This is Baby Eisz.
Isn't he cute?
He’s so cute.
He’s so noisy!
Uhm...
Zeke...
Can...
I...
come closer to your cat?
Hello...
You’re so pretty.
You look like you
came from a zoo.
What’s your name?
By the way, I’m Aemie.
And you are?
You’re so quiet.
Idiot.
It’s not going to answer you.
That’s it, I’m really
reaching my limit.
I’m seriously at my limit.
He keeps calling me an idiot.
I have a name.
It’s Aemie, right?
Aemie.
Hey, woman.
Why are you pouting over there?
You’re so annoying.
- Why?
- Because,
you keep calling me an idiot.
You can't even
tell the damn time.
Where have you been?
Didn’t I tell you
to go home early?
"Later."
"So don't you dare
go somewhere else."
Yeah, I memorized your note.
Your handwriting is so nice.
It looks like a girl’s.
Because my classmates,
their handwriting is so ugly.
It looks like it went
through a storm.
I don't care!
Where have you been?
So many questions.
Is this an interview?
I came from the park.
I was with Moo.
Moo?
What kind of a
stupid name is Moo?
Moo.
That’s my nickname
for Nico Jeisz Young,
my best friend.
He gave this to me, Baby Eisz.
Oh, that's sweet.
So he gave you this damn dog?
Yeah.
That's sweet.
Yeah. He’s sweet, right?
And you know
what, Zeke, earlier,
when he saw this wedding ring,
he suddenly got sad.
Then he suddenly started crying.
I didn’t even understand why.
I think he got jealous.
Maybe
we could buy him
a wedding ring too
so he won’t be jealous of me.
Because earlier, you
know, I offered this to him.
I was going to give it
to him, but he refused.
Let me just clear this.
Your best friend is a guy?
Yeah.
Just like you and Kaizer.
Who the fuck said
Lamperouge is my best friend?
Isn’t he?
So,
this Nico Jeisz Young.
What is this, you’re
always together?
Yeah.
You know, you
two would get along.
Why did you ask?
Oh, the cat.
- What is it?
- He said talk to him.
Huh?
Kitty, you’re so cute.
You, you’re listening to
other people’s conversation.
That’s bad.
Does your cat have a name?
None.
Wow, you didn’t
even give it one.
I don't care.
You give it a name.
Oh, okay.
What should it be?
I got it, I got it!
Amiel.
Let’s go with Amiel!
Your name is Amiel now.
That’s right, your name
is Amiel. Do you like it?
Is Amiel okay, Zeke?
Amiel?
Amiel.
So,
you gave this dog a name that’s
close to your guy best friend’s name.
And you just gave
this cat that I gifted you
a random fucking name?
What the fuck is an Amiel?
It would’ve been
better if it was...
Kiel or...
uhh...
I don’t know, you know what?
Whatever. Do whatever you want.
Amiel is a combination
of our names.
Because, right, Aemie
plus Ezekiel equals Amiel?
That was smart, right?
I came up with that.
Don’t you like it, Zeke?
I thought you’d like it.
Does Zeke have someone
else he’s courting?
Maybe that’s why
they went out earlier!
For a dinner date?!
Is that him?
No matter what you do to me,
you won’t be able to stop us...
from killing your wife!
Lamperouge.
I have a job for
you, but do it quietly.
Hey, Zeke. Coffee.
I just have something to ask.
What?
When are we going
on our honeymoon?
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Where’s a good place to go?
They said online it
should be fun and exciting.
Hi, Zeke!
I just dropped by
to bring you lunch.
Look, Mr. Roswell already
has lunch so...
he won’t be eating that.
Hey.
What the fuck?
Mr. Roswell.
Let’s talk.
MkvDrama.net